runtamil.com 2019-06-28

# Privacy Policy | runtamil,Tamil Radios Online

EU visitors And non-EU visitors cookies  
playtamilfm.com has concern that you care about how your personal information is used and shared and we take care your personal information very strongly. Users must agree with our privacy policy as following below.

Personal identification information

LiveOnlineRadio does not collect user personal identification information automatically. User personal information like name, email address and message is collected only when user voluntarily submit through our contact form. We may reply to user via email in return of their messages. However, we collect these information to enhance user experience.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, IP address, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site.

How we protect your information

Our Site is in observance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users. We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

Third-Party Links / Google Adsense

Ads appear on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve advertisements to Users based on their visit to our Site. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, location etc. You may know about the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

This privacy policy is updated on 12th Jan 2017 and we reserve the right to change our privacy policy with a prior notice. If you have any question about our privacy policy please contact tvomp3@gmail.com

#### Tamil Radios Online,

www runtamil com,
